[{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679082248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":8161,"timeElapsed":294106},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679087117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4865,"timeElapsed":298974},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3656,"timeElapsed":302633},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679142458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":51681,"timeElapsed":354316},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679150070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7609,"timeElapsed":361927},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679152011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1938,"timeElapsed":363869},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679157906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5892,"timeElapsed":369764},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679159950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2041,"timeElapsed":371808},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679162353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2399,"timeElapsed":374210},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679169843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6048,"timeElapsed":381701},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679173470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3625,"timeElapsed":385328},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679175881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2408,"timeElapsed":387739},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679178728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2845,"timeElapsed":390586},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679182292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3562,"timeElapsed":394150},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679184711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2416,"timeElapsed":396569},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679190112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5399,"timeElapsed":401970},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679193970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3856,"timeElapsed":405828},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679196086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2113,"timeElapsed":407944},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679201782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4810,"timeElapsed":413640},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679208599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6815,"timeElapsed":420457},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679211234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2632,"timeElapsed":423092},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2216,"timeElapsed":425310},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679217692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":4237,"timeElapsed":429550},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679219744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2049,"timeElapsed":431602},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679222529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":2782,"timeElapsed":434387},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679225194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2663,"timeElapsed":437052},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679228169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2972,"timeElapsed":440026},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679249597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":20384,"timeElapsed":461455},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679252708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3109,"timeElapsed":464566},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679257560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4850,"timeElapsed":469418},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679261442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3880,"timeElapsed":473300},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679264401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2957,"timeElapsed":476259},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679266732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":478590},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679306168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":39434,"timeElapsed":518026},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679308125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1954,"timeElapsed":519983},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679310296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2169,"timeElapsed":522154},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679333395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":21872,"timeElapsed":545253},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679335575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2177,"timeElapsed":547432},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679339560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3983,"timeElapsed":551417},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679349547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":9986,"timeElapsed":561405},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679352268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2719,"timeElapsed":564126},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679356747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4476,"timeElapsed":568605},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679363133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":6384,"timeElapsed":574990},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679365558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2423,"timeElapsed":577416},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679369234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3674,"timeElapsed":581092},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679383581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":13414,"timeElapsed":595439},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679386382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2798,"timeElapsed":598240},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679394107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":7722,"timeElapsed":605965},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679396668,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2559,"timeElapsed":608526},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679400359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3689,"timeElapsed":612217},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679408414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":8052,"timeElapsed":620271},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679414280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5864,"timeElapsed":626138},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679420438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6156,"timeElapsed":632296},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679425408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4968,"timeElapsed":637266},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679428144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2734,"timeElapsed":640002},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679444808,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":8712,"timeElapsed":656666},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679449873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5062,"timeElapsed":661731},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679457880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8005,"timeElapsed":669738},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679460975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3092,"timeElapsed":672833},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679469966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":8989,"timeElapsed":681824},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679473172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3203,"timeElapsed":685029},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679481405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":8231,"timeElapsed":693263},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679484101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2693,"timeElapsed":695959},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679489770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5666,"timeElapsed":701628},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679511960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":16475,"timeElapsed":723818},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679515381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3418,"timeElapsed":727238},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679518776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3393,"timeElapsed":730634},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679523731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4953,"timeElapsed":735589},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679526587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2854,"timeElapsed":738445},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679529347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2757,"timeElapsed":741205},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679537898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8549,"timeElapsed":749756},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679541628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3727,"timeElapsed":753486},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679544603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2972,"timeElapsed":756461},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679554567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7997,"timeElapsed":766425},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679560532,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5963,"timeElapsed":772390},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679568216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":7681,"timeElapsed":780074},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679571087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2869,"timeElapsed":782945},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679573625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2535,"timeElapsed":785483},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679576591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2964,"timeElapsed":788449},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679579821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3227,"timeElapsed":791678},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679583121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3298,"timeElapsed":794979},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679587321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4197,"timeElapsed":799179},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679590176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2853,"timeElapsed":802034},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679621828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":23741,"timeElapsed":833686},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679624707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2877,"timeElapsed":836565},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679628756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4046,"timeElapsed":840614},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679632041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3283,"timeElapsed":843899},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679635359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3316,"timeElapsed":847217},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679638095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2734,"timeElapsed":849952},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679640792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2695,"timeElapsed":852650},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679643027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2233,"timeElapsed":854885},{"subjectID":"kzynj175pn","prolificID":"652fe805e19cd8c9d83c1456","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b295bf4e5272806fe7a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679645668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2639,"timeElapsed":857526}]